[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Have you tried to get online yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Well, actually the president tried to get online and my daughter tried to get online.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "How on earth has this happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, it's not for -- it's not a good result as far as I think something very bad for the American people, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNPS", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Does the shambles of what is going on in any way justify shutting down the government?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "You know, I think as time goes by, I think more and more people are going to see that fighting over the implementation of a law that would be terrible for the American people is worth it and so this is going to require legislative action and you're going to see Democrats coming to the table because they're going to be shamed into admitting that the President lied and that it's a law that would be a disaster for the American people and a lot of these Democrats want to try to get reelected so they're going to come back to the table.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Did he tell the American people repeatedly a bare faced lie in your eyes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Well, I mean either he lied to the American people or is that he's so grossly negligent in doing his job that it's akin to a lie, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VBG", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Should Kathleen Sebelius resign or be fired over this, given she's now said that she must to be held person accountable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "DT", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "I think the honorable thing to do in a case like this, when you've been given the honor and the privilege to serve as a secretary, a cabinet secretary in the United States for any president, I think there's a certain amount of honor and dignity and saying, \"Look, this is a big mess.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathleen Sebelius"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Could you see a position where Ted Cruz is your party's nominee to be president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "I don't know who's going to be the nominee, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "So let me start with you, Congressman Pallone, what would you make about Reince Priebus said there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "I mean, it's all a bunch of nonsense, I mean the fact of the matter is that to the Affordable Care Act is working.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pallone", "Reince Priebus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Look, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What about telling the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "... have to do with insurance policy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Am I looking at poo and crusted vomit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "That's exactly was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Yes here, can you put the glass onto?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "How do we get America back to work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "I think the first thing you have to do is make sure you're looking at a complete narrative.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "What is going on with the education system in America that is leading to this kind of statistics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I don't think things like the skills gap or infrastructure, or currency devaluation, or manufacturing outsourcing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Would you ever consider plummeting the debts of working in Washington DC?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Good Lord, I'm just going to sip from my champagne.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "And if you do, what would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Retire.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "So this manure came from where?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "This came from a zoo.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "What sort of animal produced it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Well, once in awhile you might get an elephant dung.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Can it be that again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "In with new technology now, the way to do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "We're still the greatest manufacturing force on the planet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Walmart"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CC", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "What's the but?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CC", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "The but is Walmart has committed to bring back 50 billion jobs and manufacturing in the next 10 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$50 billion"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "$50 billion worth of manufacture...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "You think that's a good argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Maybe, but I think a better argument is, you know, well, the show that you work on for instance and many shows that if they're very, very popular, not a crisis and all but it's interesting to see an American Idol for instance or an America's Got Talent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Someone is going lose and then they'll feel bad and then what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "My kids have to learn about losing as well as winning, it makes the winning sweeter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Has it been everything you hoped it would be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Yes, it's a lot of work and it's a crowded market now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Has it drawn out more racism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Or has it begun to deal with it properly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I think it's impossible for me just as an individual to gauge whether it's more or less.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "To the question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Keep that on a little (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "When is the last time Jack did something like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "About 40 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Johnny Carson"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "CD", "IN", ":", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Was it Carson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "It may one of -- be Johnny Carson.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "It will, wouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Let's do it on CNN.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hilary"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Let's talk about your dream guest who will it be right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Well, I'd love to have Hilary come play any instrument, that would be great, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "What do you make at Chris Brown?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Brown"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Tyson", "Chris Brown"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Why should I not think terrible things about Chris Brown?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "Well, by the way Mike Tyson just came out and said, \"He's worried about Chris Brown.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Brown"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Do you have any sympathy for it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Yeah, because gosh he's such a talented entertainer and you got to think that somewhere in his past there's some kind of pain and I don't think he's a bad kid, I think he's a kid doing bad thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "And what do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Well, he's going to have to preach the nine commandments and I think that's going to be a strange, but that was in the (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "You still do stand-up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Oh I love doing stand-up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday", "Sunday", "Sunday"], "PERSON": ["Jay Leno"], "TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "And how could you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I call -- well, you know, what I go on Sunday nights with Jay Leno down to a place called Comedy and Magic or because he's there every Sunday and sometimes I go out to the ice house I love to still get on the stage on a Sunday night and get ready for the week, and if I can go out after our show some nights, I'll do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["R. Kelly"], "LOCATION": ["America", "Queens"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "PRP$", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "What about Eddie Murphy, you obviously was so brilliant together, is there chance, any plan you've spoken about doing something again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Oh, we always talk about doing comedy America, as a matter of fact on the third class of wine you come up with some really great scripts, R. Kelly takes your wife and you have to come find her in Queens.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eddie Murphy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"], "PERSON": ["Paulina Rubio"], "LOCATION": ["Cal", "Murphy"]}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "What are you doing to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "He is coming on Friday and in the next three weeks I have -- he is bringing Paulina Rubio, and I have everybody from Cal to Murphy, everything in between, every type t-shirt in between, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "What a movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "Anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "You don't followed it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Who is pound for pound the funniest person you've ever seen in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "A lot of stand-up say that, is he deemed to be the unofficial king?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", ":", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "What made him brilliant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "Well, first of all he wasn't afraid to go places in the world of honesty that some comments (ph) won't go to, like if my mother run a whole house I might not tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131030pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "You know what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "You're one of my comedic legends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]